{
	"general":
	[
		{
			"_id":1,
			"Question":"Who is the father of Geometry",
			"OptionA":"Aristotle",
			"OptionB":"Euclid",
			"OptionC":"Pythagoras",
			"OptionD":"Kepler",
			"Answer":"B"
		},
		{
			"_id":2,
			"Question":"Who was known as Iron man of India",
			"OptionA":"Ballabh Pant",
			"OptionB":"Jawaharlal Nehru",
			"OptionC":"Subhash Chandra Bose",
			"OptionD":"Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel",
			"Answer":"D"
		},
		{
			"_id":3,
			"Question":"
Jude Felix is  famous in",
			"OptionA":"Volleyball",
			"OptionB":"Tennis",
			"OptionC":"Football",
			"OptionD":"Hockey",
			"Answer":"D"
		},
		{
			"_id":4,
			"Question":"Where is the Railway Staff College located",
			"OptionA":"Pune",
			"OptionB":"Allahabad",
			"OptionC":"Vadodara",
			"OptionD":"Delhi",
			"Answer":"C"
		},
		{
			"_id":5,
			"Question":"The famous Dilwara Temples are situated in",
			"OptionA":"Uttar Pradesh",
			"OptionB":"Rajasthan",
			"OptionC":"Maharashtra",
			"OptionD":"Madhya Pradesh",
			"Answer":"B"
		},
		{
			"_id":6,
			"Question":" Amartya Sen is famous in",
			"OptionA":"Biochemistry",
			"OptionB":"Electronics",
			"OptionC":"Economics",
			"OptionD":"Geology",
			"Answer":"C"
		},
		{
			"_id":7,
			"Question":"Satyajit Ray is associated with",
			"OptionA":"Classical music",
			"OptionB":"Commercial art",
			"OptionC":"Film Direction",
			"OptionD":"Classical dance",
			"Answer":"C"
		},
		{
			"_id":8,
			"Question":"Founder of Haryak Dynasty",
			"OptionA":"Ajatshatru",
			"OptionB":"Harshvardhan",
			"OptionC":"Bimbisar",
			"OptionD":"Ghananand",
			"Answer":"C"
		},
		{
			"_id":9,
			"Question":"The Rowlatt Act was passed in",
			"OptionA":"1905",
			"OptionB":"1913",
			"OptionC":"1919",
			"OptionD":"1925",
			"Answer":"C"
		},
		{
			"_id":10,
			"Question":" A. Nageshwara Rao is associated with",
			"OptionA":"Sports",
			"OptionB":"Literature",
			"OptionC":"Film Actor",
			"OptionD":"Politics",
			"Answer":"C"
		},
		{
			"_id":11,
			"Question":"Jamini Roy was a famous",
			"OptionA":"Producer",
			"OptionB":"Painter",
			"OptionC":"Dancer",
			"OptionD":"Actor",
			"Answer":"B"
		},
		{
			"_id":12,
			"Question":"East India Association was set up in ",
			"OptionA":"1866",
			"OptionB":"1857",
			"OptionC":"1836",
			"OptionD":"1885",
			"Answer":"A"
		},
		{
			"_id":13,
			"Question":"Who called Subhash Chandra Bose as Desh Nayak ",
			"OptionA":"Lala Lajpat Rai",
			"OptionB":"Rabindranath Tagore",
			"OptionC":"Mahatma Gandhi",
			"OptionD":"Bal Gangadhar Tilak",
			"Answer":"B"
		},
		{
			"_id":14,
			"Question":"Not associated with the UNO",
			"OptionA":"ILO",
			"OptionB":"WHO",
			"OptionC":"ASEAN",
			"OptionD":"All of the above",
			"Answer":"C"
		},
		{
			"_id":15,
			"Question":"Sarojini Naidu was elected Congress President at ",
			"OptionA":"Haripura, 1938",
			"OptionB":"Bombay, 1934",
			"OptionC":"Madras Session, 1927",
			"OptionD":"Kanpur Session ,1925",
			"Answer":"D"
		},
		{
			"_id":16,
			"Question":"The Halifax summit was that of",
			"OptionA":"G-7 countries",
			"OptionB":"Leaders of the NAM",
			"OptionC":"Palestinian",
			"OptionD":"Israeli leaders",
			"Answer":"A"
		},
		{
			"_id":17,
			"Question":"Office of the UN General Assembly is in",
			"OptionA":"Vienna",
			"OptionB":"New York",
			"OptionC":"Paris",
			"OptionD":"Zurich",
			"Answer":"B"
		},
		{
			"_id":18,
			"Question":"Indian Dyarchy was started by",
			"OptionA":"Indian Council Act
",
			"OptionB":"Minto-Morley Reforms",
			"OptionC":"Indian Council Act",
			"OptionD":"Montague Reforms",
			"Answer":"D"
		},
		{
			"_id":19,
			"Question":"Ms. Vijaya Mehta is known for",
			"OptionA":"Theatre",
			"OptionB":"Film Direction",
			"OptionC":"Classical Dance",
			"OptionD":"Journalism",
			"Answer":"A"
		},
		{
			"_id":20,
			"Question":"Indian Institute of Science is located at",
			"OptionA":"Kerala",
			"OptionB":"Madras",
			"OptionC":"Bangalore",
			"OptionD":"New Delhi",
			"Answer":"C"
		},
		{
			"_id":21,
			"Question":"Electronic City of India",
			"OptionA":"Mumbai",
			"OptionB":"Hyderabad",
			"OptionC":"Guragon",
			"OptionD":"Bangalore",
			"Answer":"D"
		},
		{
			"_id":22,
			"Question":"Indian School of Mines is located in",
			"OptionA":"Dhanbad",
			"OptionB":"Asansol",
			"OptionC":"Tatanagar",
			"OptionD":"Rourkela",
			"Answer":"A"
		},
		{
			"_id":23,
			"Question":"Golden Temple is situated in",
			"OptionA":"New Delhi",
			"OptionB":"Agra",
			"OptionC":"Amritsar",
			"OptionD":"Mumbai",
			"Answer":"C"
		},
		{
			"_id":24,
			"Question":"Headquarters of the UNESCO is at",
			"OptionA":"Rome",
			"OptionB":"Geneva",
			"OptionC":"New York",
			"OptionD":"Paris",
			"Answer":"D"
		},
		{
			"_id":25,
			"Question":"UN body deals with population problem",
			"OptionA":"UNFPA",
			"OptionB":"UNDP",
			"OptionC":"UNICEF",
			"OptionD":"UNESCO",
			"Answer":"A"
		},
	]
}